# Zoë Morken

# User Interface & Visual Designer

## **Projects**

August 2019 -December 2019

**UX Designer**, UX Experience Studio Project sponsored by Cerner Corporation

Researched and designed a healthcare communication channel to improve the timeliness and efficacy of student doctor appointments by optimizing scheduling based on individual needs.

Narrowed the problem scope down to guiding college students through taking charge of their health and led the development of persona development for our final solution.

October 2019 -December 2019 **UX Designer**, UX Learning Studio Project: API For The Win

Constructed an engaging web experience using Spotify's Web API that allows users to create a playlist based on their current activity.

Learned to make backend API calls with Ajax requests, handle Spotify's authentication protocol, and deploy the solution to

## Experience

June 2019 - Present Freelance Web Designer, Little Peeps Photography

Built an attractive storefront website showcasing client's work, streamline the booking process, and sell photography services.

September 2018 -March 2019

**Graphic Artist**, The Purdue Exponent

Developed bold and fun graphics for both media and print with the use of Adobe Creative Cloud Tools. Collaborated with reporters and editors in order to create pieces that best complemented their stories.

#### **Activities**

January 2019 -Present

**Student Ambassador**, Purdue Polytechnic Ambassadors Program

Represented the Polytechnic Institute by communicating with prospective students during various recruitment events. Gave overview presentations and answered questions about my experience to large (100+) groups of prospective students and parents during information sessions.

Distributed handouts and promotional materials to counselors at local high school.

zoemorken.github.io zmorken@purdue.edu (720) 320-0337

### Education

Pursuing B.S. User Experience Design, Purdue University

Minors in Communication and Psychology August 2018 – Present GPA: 3.94 Dean's List & Semester Honors (all semesters)

## **Skills**

#### Research

Surveys, Interviews, Affinity Diagramming, Competitive Analysis, Bodystorming, Heuristic Evaluation, Personas, Usability Testing

### Design

Sketches, Wireframes, Low to High Fidelity Mockups, Ideation

#### Communication

Critical Writing, Stakeholder Presentations, Sponsor Meetings

#### Tools

## Prototyping

Photoshop, Illustrator, Adobe XD, Figma, Balsamiq

## Development

HTML, CSS, JS, JQuery, CSS Frameworks (Skeleton, Bootstrap)

#### Personal Interests

Dancing, Hiking, Weightlifting Olive (my dog) Photography Playing Piano Reading